[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chiraptophobia means fear of snow.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what part of the human body are Von Ebners glands located?", "correct_answer": "Tongue", "incorrect_answers": ["Skin", "All of these", "Nasal cavity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A Clydesdale horse can weight up to 1,000 pounds (500 kg).", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character is killed in the 1999 movie Star Wars Episode I: The Phantom Menace, which is among the highest-grossing movies of all time?", "correct_answer": "Qui-Gon Jinn", "incorrect_answers": ["Jar Jar Binks", "Obi-Wan Kenobi", "Anakin Skywalker"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the reason why Maori women tattoo their faces.", "correct_answer": "To conceal age wrinkles", "incorrect_answers": ["To prevent the access of sunlight to their faces", "To be more attractive to men", "To indicate their social status"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is Venus the coldest planet in the Solar System?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these body systems do jellyfish NOT have?", "correct_answer": "all of these", "incorrect_answers": ["osmoregulatory", "respiratory", "circulatory"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed the cannibalistic Dr. Hannibal Lecter in the 1991 horror movie The Silence of the Lambs?", "correct_answer": "Anthony Hopkins", "incorrect_answers": ["Dustin Hoffman", "Jack Nicholson", "Gene Hackman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This buttonless and collarless piece of clothing was originally worn as an undershirt.", "correct_answer": "T-shirt", "incorrect_answers": ["Girdle", "Slip", "Hosiery"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which country does the Clydesdale horse originate from?", "correct_answer": "Scotland", "incorrect_answers": ["Ireland", "Spain", "England"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This form of alternative medicine focuses on stimulating different areas of the feet.", "correct_answer": "Reflexology", "incorrect_answers": ["Therapeutic touch", "Iridology", "Osteopathy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why should the consumption of celery seeds and oil be avoided during pregnancy?", "correct_answer": "They may trigger uterine contractions.", "incorrect_answers": ["They may be toxic to the fetus.", "They raise blood pressure.", "All of these"]}]